metv.com 2019-12-31

# Privacy Policy

Updated: December 31, 2019

We take your electronic privacy seriously. Questions regarding this statement or our practices should be directed to the MeTV.com Privacy Coordinator by email at feedback-metv@metvnetwork.com. You may also send inquiries by mail to:

 **Privacy Coordinator**

 **MeTV National Limited Partnership**

 **26 North Halsted**

 **Chicago, IL 60661**

You may also call our toll free number: 1-833-367-6388

We reserve the right to change our policy from time to time as we deem appropriate in our sole discretion.

KINDS OF INFORMATION

There are two kinds of information websites can obtain about you:

·       Aggregate Information: Aggregate Information is anonymous data that websites use to diagnose problems on the sites' servers, administer the sites, and to help improve the quality of the Web pages. It may be your domain name (i.e. "XYZ.com") or your IP address.

·       Personally Identifiable Information: Personally Identifiable Information is any information that personally identifies you. It can be your first and last name, your email address, your home address, or your telephone number. Sometimes this personal information is needed when you order products online or subscribe to an email newsletter. Other times, websites collect this information to help personalize advertising and marketing.

We collect Aggregate Information - such as your IP address (a number that's automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're surfing the Internet), browser type (e.g., Netscape or Internet Explorer), and domain (e.g., "XYZ.com"). We do this in the background so it does not interrupt your cruising speed. We use this information to help diagnose problems with our servers, to administer our site, and to gather broad demographic information. We share Aggregate Information with third parties for advertising and promotional purposes. None of this information is connected with Personally Identifiable Information. So, when you enter our site, you are anonymous and will remain that way unless you choose otherwise.

SURVEYS AND REGISTRATION FORMS

Sometimes MeTV.com posts surveys and registration forms in which we ask for Personally Identifiable Information. Here are some ways we might use that information:

·       To send you information about MeTV Network and this website.

·       To better serve viewers on the MeTV network.

·       To customize which articles and information appears on this website for visitors.

The choice is yours - you do not have to answer surveys or register for newsletters or service. If you choose to answer the survey or complete the registration, we will tell you on the survey or registration form how we will use the Personally Identifiable Information. If we are asking for optional information, we will mark it with an asterisk (*) so you know you can skip it if you want. And on that same page we will give you a way to "opt out" of being contacted by MeTV.com and any third parties.

CONTESTS AND SWEEPSTAKES

From time to time we run contests and sweepstakes in which we ask for Personally Identifiable Information such as your name, email address or telephone number. That's so we can let you know if you win. Sometimes we request additional Personally Identifiable Information such as your age, gender, and income level. And once in a while - though not often - we require this additional information in exchange for allowing you to enter the contest. Here are some of the ways we might use the information that we collect:

·       To notify you if you are a winner

·       To send you information about MeTV Network and our site

·       To give to content partners, who may send you promotional email

·       To give to advertisers, who may send you emails about their products and services

We may share Aggregate Information with our partners and advertisers. We will not share your Personally Identifiable Information with third parties unless we tell you otherwise when asking for it. We will give you a way to "opt out" of being contacted by MeTV.com and any third parties.

If you win one of our contests or sweepstakes, we will not publish your name, hometown, or other Personally Identifiable Information on the Site unless you give us your permission.

OPT OUT

If we ask you for Personally Identifiable Information, we will tell you if we intend to share it with others. We will provide you with a way to tell us that you don't want us to share the information or if you don't want to receive promotional and/or marketing information about products, services, and offerings from MeTV.com and/or any third parties. Let us know and we will use your name and address only to tell you if you win a contest.

COOKIES AND INFORMATION

We authorize select suppliers of advertisements to place cookies on MeTV.com. The purpose of the cookies is to re/target users of our website to display personalized advertisements in their future navigation based on your visit to this website. The following platforms - IAB opt-out platform, Network Advertising Initiative opt-out platform, and Digital Advertising Alliance platform provide options to express opt-out choices for all companies that are registered in the respective platform. Please note that if you disable the display of personalized ads and other advertising partners, you will continue to receive ads that are less relevant to your interests/browsing behavior.

Here is a list of suppliers authorized to place cookies on MeTV.com and information on how to opt-out through their privacy policy.

·       Criteo (criteo.com/en/privacy-policy)

·       Sovrn (sovrn.com/privacy-policy)

·       Rubicon ([https://rubiconproject.com/rubicon-project-advertising-technology-privacy-policy/platform-cookie-statement/](https://rubiconproject.com/rubicon-project-advertising-technology-privacy-policy/platform-cookie-statement/))

·       App Nexus ([https://www.appnexus.com/platform-privacy-policy#choices](https://www.appnexus.com/platform-privacy-policy#choices))

·       Amazon ([https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=468496#GUID-1B2BDAD4-7ACF-4D7A-8608-CBA6EA897FD3__SECTION_0D132936501A4AE0A2F8D74426A8A2CA](https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=468496#GUID-1B2BDAD4-7ACF-4D7A-8608-CBA6EA897FD3__SECTION_0D132936501A4AE0A2F8D74426A8A2CA))

·       Google Ads([https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en](https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en) and https://adssettings.google.com) 

SUBPOENAS AND LAW ENFORCEMENT AGENCIES

We reserve the right to cooperate with government and law enforcement agencies engaged in investigations of activities that are, or are believed to be, illegal. Further, we may share your Personally Identifiable Information with such agencies if we believe that a crime or any act that endangers the health and safety of others may have been or may be committed. We may also share your Personally Identifiable Information in response to an appropriate subpoena.

COMMUNITY AND PUBLIC AREAS

Information posted to message boards or chat areas is available to the general public. Please use caution when posting any such information. Users under the age of 18 should be particularly careful not to provide any personally identifying information while using chat rooms or message boards. We reserve the right to, but are not obligated to, refuse or delete any content that in our sole discretion is considered inappropriate. Please see our Terms of Service for additional information.

FEEDBACK AND EMAIL

On every page at MeTV.com there is a link to a Contact Us email form so you can comment, complain, make suggestions, and ask questions. Your email address is required on this form so we can answer your questions, and we want your name, too, so we can address our answer in a mannerly way. We may also track your browser type and referring URL to better diagnose technical issues you may be having. We do not share this information with third parties and we will use it only to answer your correspondence.

LINKS TO OTHER SITES

When you visit our site, you may be directed to other sites outside our service. For example, if you click on a banner advertisement, you will leave our site. This includes links to sites operated by advertisers, sponsors and partners that may use our logo as part of an agreement with us. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. These other sites are not subject to our privacy policy and we are not responsible for the privacy policies for these other sites, nor for the use of any information that these sites may collect.

DELETING OR MODIFYING YOUR INFORMATION

If you've given us personally identifiable information in the past and then have second thoughts or want to update it, here are your choices:

Email to:

feedback-metv@metvnetwork.com with subject line “Privacy Coordinator”

Regular mail to:

MeTV National Limited Partnership

26 North Halsted

Chicago, IL 60661

Phone call to:

1-833-367-6388

Although it is not always possible to remove or modify information in the databases, we will make reasonable efforts to do so. If you've given us information for one of those third parties we mentioned above and we've already passed it on, we may not be able to delete or change the information.

SECURITY OF PRIVATE INFORMATION

Any personal information you give us is kept in secure files. Access is limited to the few employees who have a need to know. We would like to tell you that your information is as safe with us as it is in your head, but, as hackers have proved worldwide, no computer security system is entirely foolproof. The most any Website can do is make reasonable efforts, which is what we do at MeTV.com, to protect your information from theft, misuse and alteration.

CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

The State of California permits California residents to request from a business, with whom the California resident has an established business relationship, certain information about the types of personal information the business has shared with third parties for those third parties’ direct marketing purposes and the names and addresses of the third parties with whom the business has shared such information during the immediately preceding calendar year.  You may make the request:

1.    By emailing us at: feedback-metv@metvnetwork.com with the subject line “Privacy Coordinator Request” 

2.    By completing the contact form at this page: [https://metv.com/contact](https://metv.com/contact) and selecting “Privacy Request” as the reason for your message. 

3.    By sending inquiries by mail to:

Privacy Coordinator

MeTV National Limited Partnership

26 North Halsted

Chicago, IL 60661

4.    You may also call our toll free number: 1-833-367-6388

California residents also have the right to request that we (a) delete all personal information; (b) provide a copy of all personal information we collected; or (c) opt them out of any sale of their personal information. If you are a California Resident who would like to exercise one of these rights, you may contact us: 

1.    By emailing us at: feedback-metv@metvnetwork.com with the subject line “Privacy Coordinator Request” 

2.    By completing the contact form at this page: [https://metv.com/contact](https://metv.com/contact) and selecting “Privacy Request” as the reason for your message. 

3.    By sending inquiries by mail to:

Privacy Coordinator / MeTV National Limited Partnership

26 North Halsted

Chicago, IL 60661

4.    By calling our toll free number: 1-833-367-6388

You will not be discriminated against as a result of your choice to exercise these rights, however certain account and personalization functionality may be lost as a result of your request to delete your information or opt-out of sale of your information.

In accordance with the California law, we are required to verify your identity before processing a request for deletion or request for information. We will attempt to do so based on your account information (where applicable) and the information you provide when submitting the request, however there may be instances where we do not have sufficient personal information about you in order to reasonably verify your identity. In such cases, we will let you know and treat a request for deletion as a do not sell request. In addition, there may be instances when we need to retain such information for legal compliance or business purposes.
